Guide to the Time Inc. People Publishing and Business Records 1973-2003 MS 3009-RG 27
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Publisher Richard Durrell Files, 1973-1983; 56.25 Linear feet in 57 record cartons
  - Subseries I.B. Subject Files, 1973-1983; 55.25 Linear feet in 56 record cartons
    - Memoranda: Gallagher, John, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda: Garner, Nate [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda: Gentalen, Tiit, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda: Glatzhofer, Ed [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda: Goltra, Libby, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda: Graves, Ralph, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda: Heiskell, Andrew, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda: Karageorge, Penelope, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda: Keylor, Art, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 10-12)
    - Memoranda: Labich, Dick, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Luce, Henry, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda: Marketing Services, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda: McCluskey, Jim, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 16)
    - Memoranda: Meigher, Chris, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 17)
    - Memoranda: Miller, Bill, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 18)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda: Mulcahy, Eileen, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 20)
    - Memoranda: Munro, Dick, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 21)
    - Memoranda: Nunes, Lucy, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 22)
    - Memoranda: Production, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 23)
    - Memoranda: Promotion, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 24)
    - Memoranda: Publicity, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 25)
    - Memoranda: Rueffer, Terry, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 26)
    - Memoranda: Schenck, John, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 27)
    - Memoranda: Shepley, Jim, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 28)
    - Memoranda: Sidey, Hugh, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 29)
    - Memoranda: Slovinsky, Lou, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 30)
    - Memoranda: Stoklos, Mary, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 31)
    - Memoranda: Stolley, Dick, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 32)
    - Memoranda: Strauss, Ed: Weekly Report, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 33)
    - Memoranda: Sutton, Kelso, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 34)
    - Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 35-36)
    - Memoranda: Thorkilsen, Eric, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 1-3)
    - Memoranda: Verdon, John, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda: Znachko, Mike, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 5)
    - Merchandising, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 7)
    - Money, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 8)
    - Monger and Waterhouse, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 9)
    - Monthly Reports: Ad Sales, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 10)
    - Movie Category, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 11)
    - Music Special Issue, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 12)
    - National Enquirer, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 13)
    - Nashville [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 14)
    - National Golf Links, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 15)
    - National Star, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 16)
    - New Orleans, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 17)
    - Newsstand Draw [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 18)
    - Newsweek, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 19)
    - New York Times, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 20)
    - Out of Town Schedule, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 21)
    - Parties, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 22)
    - Parties: Miami Boat Trip: November 6, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 23)
    - Parties: Copacabana: November 25, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 24)
    - People Poll Issue 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 25-26)
    - People Shopper, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 27)
    - People Suite, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 28)
    - People to People, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 29)
    - Permissions, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 30)
    - Personnel, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 31)
    - Photographers, Fees, Etc., 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 32)
    - PIB, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 33)
    - Playboy Enterprises, Inc., 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 34)
    - Postal Service, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 35)
    - Posters, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 36)
    - Presentations, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 37)
    - Presentations: Industry, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 38)
    - Presentations: Other Magazines [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 39)
    - Presentations: The Big Show, 1980 (Offsite-box 2977, Folder 40-41)
    - Photo Contest, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 1)
    - Photo Exhibit, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 2)
    - Positioning, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 3)
    - President's Lunch, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 4)
    - Price Increase [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 5)
    - Price Tests, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 6)
    - Pricing, Regulations, Test, Etc., 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 7)
    - Print Order, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 8-9)
    - Print Order: Plants, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 10)
    - Production, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 11)
    - Profile, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 12)
    - Progressive Grocer, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 13)
    - Promotion: Air, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 14)
    - Promotion: Circulation Subscriber Cards and Television Tests, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 15)
    - Promotion: Consumer Circulation, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 16)
    - Promotion: General, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 17)
    - Promotion: Holland and Callaway, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 18-19)
    - Promotion: Network Television Schedules, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 20)
    - Promotion: Print, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 21)
    - Promotion: Radio, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 22)
    - Promotion: Television, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 23)
    - Promotion: Trades [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 24)
    - Public Place, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 25)
    - Publicity: Air, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 26)
    - Publicity: General, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 27)
    - Publicity: Print, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 28)
    - Publisher's Lunch, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 29)
    - Raises, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 30)
    - Rates, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 31)
    - Rates: Subscriptions, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 32)
    - Rate Increase, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 33)
    - Reader's Digest, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 34)
    - Rebates: Advertising Complaints, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 35)
    - Recession [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 36)
    - Redbook, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 37)
    - Regional, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 38)
    - Renewal Space Credit, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 39)
    - Reprints, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 40)
    - Research, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 41)
    - Research: Circulation [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 42)
    - Research: Focus Groups, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 42)
    - Research: Focus Groups: January 21-24, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 43)
    - Research: Focus Group: Hartford, St. Louis, Omaha: June 24-27, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 44)
    - Research: Paine Webber: Status Report, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 45)
    - Research: Reader Perception Study, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 46)
    - Research: Scarborough Study, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 47)
    - Research: Young & Rubicam [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 48)
    - Result Stories, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 50)
    - Retail Display Allowance (RDA), 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 51)
    - Sales Figures, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 52)
    - Sales Meeting: Scottsdale, 1980 (Offsite-box 4205, Folder 7-8)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Crowley, John, 1980 (Offsite-box 4205, Folder 9-10)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Crowley, John, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 53)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Durrell, Dick, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 54)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Gallagher, John, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 55)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Gentalen, Tiit, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 56)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Marketing Services Research, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 57)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 58)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Motta, Tony [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 59)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Promotion, 1980 (Offsite-box 2978, Folder 60)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 1)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Verdon, John, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 2)
    - Screenings, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 3)
    - Selling Areas Marketing, Inc. (SAMI), 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 4)
    - Serialization, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 5)
    - Serialization: The Fifth Horseman, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 6)
    - Simmons, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 7)
    - Simmons Marketing Research Bureau, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 8)
    - Special Editions, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 9)
    - Special Units, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 10)
    - Split People, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 11)
    - Sports Illustrated, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 12)
    - Standard Rate and Data Service [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 13)
    - Starch, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 14-15)
    - Steer Meetings, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 16)
    - Store Checks, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 17)
    - Store Checks by Salesmen, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 18)
    - Subscriptions, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 19)
    - Subscriptions: Tests, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 20)
    - Supermarkets, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 21)
    - Supermarket News [EMPTY], 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 22)
    - Syndication, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 23)
    - Television and Television Shows, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 24)
    - Temple-Eastex: Arthur Temple, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 25)
    - Tests, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 26)
    - Test Markets, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 27)
    - Time, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 28)
    - Time Distribution Services: A & P, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 29)
    - Time Distribution Services: Bonus [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 30)
    - Time Distribution Services: Budget [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 31)
    - Time Distribution Services: Charles Levy Circulation Company, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 32)
    - Time Distribution Services: Checks, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 33)
    - Time Distribution Services: Correspondence, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 34)
    - Time Distribution Services: Direct Sell to Chains, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 35)
    - Time Distribution Services: Draw, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 36)
    - Time Distribution Services: Drug Stores, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 37)
    - Time Distribution Services: Front End, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 38)
    - Time Distribution Services: General, 1980 (Offsite-box 2979, Folder 39-40)
    - Time Distribution Services: International Periodicals Distributors Association (IPDA), 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 1)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 2)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings: June 9-12, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 3)
    - Time Distribution Services: Melville Audit, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 4)
    - Time Distribution Services: Monthly Reports, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 5)
    - Time Distribution Services: Monthly and Weekly Reports, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 6)
    - Time Distribution Services: Newsstand, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 7)
    - Time Distribution Services: On Line Media, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 8)
    - Time Distribution Services: People, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 9)
    - Time Distribution Services: Personnel, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 10)
    - Time Distribution Services: Promotion, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 11)
    - Time Distribution Services: Quarterly Markets Reports, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 12)
    - Time Distribution Services: Racking, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 13)
    - Time Distribution Services: Racking: Stories Covered Weekly, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 14)
    - Time Distribution Services: Research [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 15)
    - Time Distribution Services: Sports Clinic, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 16)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 17-18)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Book and Record Stores, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 19)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Box Stores, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 20)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Drug Stores, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 21)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Jewel Stores, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 22)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Kroger, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 23)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Safeway, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 24)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Sav-On, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 25)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Stop and Shop, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 26)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Super Valu Stores, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 27)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Winn-Dixie [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 28)
    - Time Distribution Services: Success Bulletins, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 29)
    - Time Distribution Services: Tip-Ons, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 30)
    - Time Distribution Services: Weekly Regional Managers Sales Estimates, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 31)
    - Time Distribution Services: Weekly Regional Sales Estimates: Us, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 32)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 33)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers: Late Delivery, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 34)
    - Time-Life Books, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 35)
    - Time-Life Film, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 36)
    - T, P, & C, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 37)
    - Trades, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 38)
    - Travel Category, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 39)
    - TV Guide, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 40)
    - Us, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 41)
    - Us: Advertising [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 42)
    - Us: Circulation, 1980 (Offsite-box 2980, Folder 43)
    - Us: Promotion, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 1)
    - Us: Publicity, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 2)
    - Us: Research, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 3)
    - Us: Sales Figures, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 4)
    - United Way, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 5)
    - Universal Product Codes (UPC), 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 6)
    - Vacations, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 7)
    - Washington Star [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 8)
    - Weekly Account Analysis Reports by Branch Managers, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 9)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 10-11)
    - Weekly Reports: Keylor, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 12)
    - West Coast, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 13)
    - Woman's Day, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 14)
    - Women's Books, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 15)
    - Women's Wear Daily, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 16)
    - Year End Review, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 17)
    - Young & Rubicam: Focus Groups, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 18)
    - Young & Rubicam: Promotion, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 19)
    - Branch Offices: Atlanta, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 20-21)
    - Branch Offices: Boston, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 22)
    - Branch Offices: Chicago, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 23)
    - Branch Offices: Detroit, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 24)
    - Branch Offices: Hartford: November 24, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 25)
    - Branch Offices: Houston, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 26)
    - Branch Offices: Los Angeles, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 27)
    - Branch Offices: Memphis, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 28)
    - Branch Offices: Minneapolis, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 29)
    - Branch Offices: New York, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 30)
    - Branch Offices: Portland: January 29-30, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 31)
    - Branch Offices: San Francisco, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 32)
    - Branch Offices: Seattle: January 27-29, 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 33)
    - Branch Offices: Texas [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 34)
    - Branch Offices: Washington, D.C., 1980 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 35)
    - Ad Council, 1981 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 36)
    - Ad Research, 1981 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 37)
    - Advertising Records, Etc., 1981 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 38)
    - Adweek, 1981 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 39)
    - Affirmative Action, 1981 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 40)
    - Airport Sale, 1981 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 41)
    - American Renewal, 1981 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 42-43)
    - Annual Report, 1981 (Offsite-box 2981, Folder 44)
    - Applications, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 1-2)
    - Automotive Category, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 3)
    - Awards, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 4)
    - Bagley Report: Food Marketing Institute, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 5)
    - Bleed, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 6)
    - Blynn, Buz: Miami Representative, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 8)
    - Budget: Ad Sales, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 9)
    - Budget: Budget Session: January 21, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 10)
    - Bonus Letters, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 11)
    - Canada, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 12)
    - Chain Store Age Supermarkets, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 13)
    - Cigarettes, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 14)
    - Cigarette Category, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 15)
    - Circulation, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 16)
    - Circulation: Direct Mail Subscriptions, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 17)
    - Circulation: EVP Report, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 18)
    - Circulation: Stats Report, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 19)
    - Clips: Census, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 20)
    - Clips: People, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 21)
    - Clips: Supermarket, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 22)
    - College, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 23)
    - Comp Copies: To Washington People: Return Letters, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 24)
    - Comp Lists, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 25)
    - Company Plane, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 26)
    - Complaints, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 27)
    - Complaint Reports: Stelle, Jerry, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 28)
    - Conventions: Dinners, Luncheons, Etc., 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 29)
    - Conventions: Trade, Etc., 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 30-31)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute Midwinter: January 6-9, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 32)
    - Conventions: Detroit Auto Show: January 9, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 33)
    - Conventions: Cosmetic, Toiletry, and Fragrance Association: Boca Raton: March 1-4, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 34)
    - Conventions: Time Inc. Conference on Election Reform: Washington, D.C.: March 20-24: Cancelled, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 35)
    - Conventions: Western Association of Food Chains: Hawaii: March 28-April 1, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 36)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Dallas: May 3-6, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 37)
    - Conventions: Housing Conference: Lyford Cay: May 6-10, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 38)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Washington, D.C.: October 4-7, 1981 (Offsite-box 2982, Folder 39)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Brunch Invitations: October 4-7, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 1)
    - Copy Acceptance, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 2)
    - Corporate Creative Services, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 3)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 4)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution: Gravure, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 5)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution: Letterpress, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 6)
    - Cosmopolitan, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 7)
    - Covers, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 8)
    - Covers: Other Magazines, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 9)
    - Couponing, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 10)
    - CPDA, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 11)
    - CPM, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 12)
    - Delivery Reports: Newsstands, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 13)
    - Direct Mail, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 14)
    - Direct Response, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 15)
    - Discounts: Frequency, Charitable, Etc., 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 16)
    - Discover, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 17)
    - Distribution, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 18)
    - Donnelly: Chicago: November 23-24, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 19)
    - Dorset Suite, Etc., 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 20)
    - Douglas, Mike Show, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 21)
    - Edit Close, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 22)
    - Edit: Close and Misses, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 23)
    - Edit: Serious People Articles, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 24)
    - EPCOT Disney Pavilion, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 25)
    - Esquire, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 26)
    - Estimates, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 27)
    - Executive Compensation, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 28)
    - Fact Sheets, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 29)
    - Family Circle, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 30)
    - Filler Space, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 31)
    - Filler Space: Others in People, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 32)
    - Financial and Development Group: Larry Crutcher, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 33)
    - Folio, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 34)
    - Food Category, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 35)
    - Fortune, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 36)
    - Fractional Units, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 37)
    - Free Contribution Requests, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 38)
    - Free Space Requests, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 39)
    - Gallagher Reports, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 40)
    - Golf, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 41)
    - Golf: Sour Marsh: April 30-May 1, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 42)
    - Golf: Detroit Golf Invitational: June 1-2, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 43)
    - Golf: Chicago: June 8-9, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 44)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Invitational: Maidstone: September 14-15, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 45)
    - Golf: La Quinta: December 2-5, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 46)
    - Hall Magazine Editorial Report, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 47)
    - Harvard Lampoon, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 48)
    - Health and Beauty Aids (HBA) Category, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 49)
    - Hold, 1981 (Offsite-box 2983, Folder 50)
    - Home Box Office (HBO), 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 1)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Directors Meeting, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 2)
    - House Space Orders, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 3)
    - Ibit, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 4)
    - Ideas For People, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 5)
    - Ideas: Murray Roberts, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 6)
    - Ideas: People Book Club, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 7)
    - Ideas: Puzzle, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 8)
    - Information Systems Division, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 9)
    - Insert Cards, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 10)
    - Inserts, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 11)
    - Intercorporate Group, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 12)
    - International: Japan, 1981 (Offsite-box 2984, Folder 13)